wikifeet.com 2017-02-02

# Draft Privacy Statement

**

Privacy Statement of Loading 5% 

_Statement No 59207_

**

**

**Information about our Organisation and Web site**

**

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organisation like Loading 5% . We are based in Israel .  Our principal activities are: 

  * Website programming 
  * Multimedia 

Our privacy policy covers Loading 5% and its Web site: 

** Organisation Name:  |  Loading 5%   
---|---  
Address:  |  47 itzhak sadde st.   
City, Zip:  |  Tel Aviv  ,  67066   
State:  |  Israel   
Country:  |  Israel   
Controller:  |  Eli Ozer   
Web Sites(s):  |  wikifeet.com   
**

Our privacy policy also covers our subsidiary and its Web site: 

**

**Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access**

**

You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data. 

**

** The services and links of our Web site  ** ****

**

Our Web site enables you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data. 

Our Web site does not include links to third party Web service providers. 

**

Automatic Collection of Information 

**

We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. 

We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. 

**

Data Collection and Purpose Specification 

**

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. 

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations. 

To access the table of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used, please  click here 

We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below. 

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose:  by indicating in a box at the point on the site where personal data is collected 

**

Children's Privacy 

**

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children. 

We do not take specific steps to protect the privacy of children who disclose their personal data to us. 

We do not provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page, or at those sites on our Web site where we collect personal data. 

**

Disclosure and Visitor Choice 

**

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organisations. 

**

Confidentiality / Security 

**

We do not give visitors to our Web site the option of using a secure transmission method to send us their personal data. 

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from: 

  * unauthorised access 
  * improper use or disclosure 
  * unauthorised modification 
  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss 

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. 

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation. 

**

Access to the personal data we may hold about you 

**

We do not grant our visitors the right to have access to the personal data that we keep about them. 

We do not provide our visitors with a readable copy of the personal data that we keep about them. 

We do not allow our visitors to challenge the data that we hold about them. 

We do not reserve the right to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data. 

**

Privacy Compliance 

**

There are no national laws or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organisation. 

There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organisation. 

We cannot demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the privacy  instrument. 

####  Primary personal data/Business information 

**x** |  volunteered by each visitor   
---|---  
\-  |  collected from public records or bodies   
\-  |  collected from private organisations   
  
####  Other personal details and profiling data 

\-  |  volunteered by each visitor   
---|---  
\-  |  collected from public records or bodies   
\-  |  collected from private organisations   
  
####  Identifiers 

**x** |  volunteered by each visitor   
---|---  
\-  |  collected from public records or bodies   
\-  |  collected from private organisations   
  
####  Specific Data 

\-  |  volunteered by each visitor   
---|---  
\-  |  collected from public records or bodies   
\-  |  collected from private organisations   
  
* * *

_

Section 7: Disclosure and Visitor Choice 

Not offering individuals the opportunity to consent to the disclosure of their personal data for new purposes is inconsistent with the OECD Use Limitation Principle. 

_

_Section 9: Access to the personal data we may hold about you_ _

Not providing visitors with an opportunity of finding out whether you hold personal data about them is inconsistent with the OECD Indidvidual Participation Principle. 

_ _

Not providing visitors with a copy of their personal data is inconsistent with the OECD Indidvidual Participation Principle. 

_ _

Not allowing visitors to challenge their personal data is inconsistent with the OECD Indidvidual Participation Principle. 

_ _

Not allowing visitors to have their personal data erased, rectified etc is inconsistent with the OECD Indidvidual Participation Principle. 

_

* * *
